sentosa.com.sg 2013-09-13

# Privacy Policy- Sentosa

### PRIVACY POLICY AND LEGAL NOTICES

#### At Sentosa, we are determined to keep your personal information safe, secure, and private.

This statement is provided to demonstrate our organization's commitment to protecting your privacy. Any information we collect on this site will be used to service your requests and to improve our website.

We want you to feel comfortable about visiting our website and giving us your personal information. No renting or selling of your name or any of your personal information to any third party will be done unless with your permission.

We may share statistical or demographic information with our marketing partners, advertisers, or other third parties. This information is in the form of statistics or purchase demographics on a group basis and is never in respect of an individual person.

If you have subscribed to one of our newsletters, or entered one of our contests, we may occasionally update you about special opportunities via email. If you would rather not be contacted, please email us at [administrator@sentosa.com.sg](mailto:administrator@sentosa.com.sg)

By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information by Sentosa. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

### DISCLAIMER AND LEGAL NOTICE

This website is the property of Sentosa. It may only be reproduced, disclosed or distributed for non-commercial use with written authorization from Sentosa . Any unauthorized reproduction, disclosure or distribution of copies by any person of any portion of this website may be a violation of the Copyright Law.

With all the material contained in these Web pages, Sentosa has attempted to offer the most timely and accurate information possible. However, inadvertent errors may occur. The information contained in these Web pages is provided without warranty of accuracy. Sentosa reserves the right to discontinue, or change at any time, product features or any information in these Web pages without notice or liabilities.

Many links from this site lead to external resources (websites) which are maintained and hosted by third parties, over which Sentosa has no control and is in no manner responsible.
